A Guide to the Secretary of Commerce and Trade, Correspondence and subject files, 1998-2002
Library of Virginia
- Series I: Constituent correspondence, 1998 Feb-2001 Dec
  - Constituent correspondence #2086519-2086990, Nov 2001 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Constituent correspondence #2087007-2087296, Nov-Dec 2001 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Constituent correspondence #2087302-2087804, Dec 2001 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Constituent correspondence #2088069-2088790, Dec 2001 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Series II: Agency correspondence and subject files, 1998-2001
  Arranged alphabetically by agency.
  - Agriculture and Consumer Serives, Dept. of, 1998-2001
    - General, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - General, 1999 Feb-Jul (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - General, 1999 Aug-Dec (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - General, 2000 Jan-Aug (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - General, 2000 Sep-Dec (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - General, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Drought, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Drought, 1999 Jan-Apr (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Drought, 1999 Jul (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Drought, 1999 Aug (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Drought, 1999 Sep-Nov (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Tobacco Idemnification and Community Revitalization Commission, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Tobacco Idemnification and Community Revitalization Commission, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Tobacco Idemnification and Community Revitalization Commission, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Business Administration, Dept. of, 1998-2001
    - General, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - General, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - General, 2000-2001 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Forestry, Dept. of, 1998-2001
    - General, 1998-1999 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - General, 2000-2001 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Housing and Community Development, Dept. of, 1993-2001
    - General, 1998-1999 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - General, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - General, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Community Development Block Grants - General, 1998 May-Jun (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Community Development Block Grants - General, 1998 Jul (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Community Development Block Grants - General, 1998 Oct (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Community Development Block Grants - First Round Briefing Packages, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Community Development Block Grants - First Round Grants, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Community Development Block Grants - Second Round Grants, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Community Development Block Grants - General, 1999 Apr (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Community Development Block Grants - General, 1999 Jul (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Community Development Block Grants - General, 1999 Aug-Oct (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Community Development Block Grants - First Round Briefing Packages, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Community Development Block Grants - First Round Grants, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Community Development Block Grants - Second Round Grants, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Community Development Block Grants - General, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Community Development Block Grants - First Round Briefing Package, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Community Development Block Grants - First Round Grants, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Community Development Block Grants - Second Round Grants, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Community Development Block Grants - Urgent need submission, Isle of Wight County, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Community Development Block Grants - General, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Community Development Block Grants - First Round Briefing Package, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Community Development Block Grants - Industrial Development Site Fund Proposal, 2001 May (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Enterprise Zone Program - General, 1994 Jan-Feb (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Enterprise Zone Program - General, 1994 Mar-Jun (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Enterprise Zone Program - General, 1994 Jul-Dec (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Enterprise Zone Program - General, 1995 Jan-Feb (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Enterprise Zone Program - General, 1995 Mar-Nov (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Enterprise Zone Program - General, 1996 Jan (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Enterprise Zone Program - General, 1996 Mar-Sep; 1997 Apr (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Enterprise Zone Program - Annual Report, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Enterprise Zone Program - Background report, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Enterprise Zone Program - Briefing binder, 1994 Jan (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Enterprise Zone Program - Briefing for Senate Finance Committee, 1994 Sep (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Enterprise Zone Program - Briefing binder, 1995 Nov (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Enterprise Zone Program - Regulations, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Enterprise Zone Program - Regulations, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Enterprise Zone Program - Testimony before Joint Subcommittee Studying Ways to Assist and Encourage Small Business, 1994 Oct (Box 12, Folder 23)